<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NFC Encrypter</string>

    <string name="read_help_title">How to read NFC tag</string>
    <string name="read_help_desc">To read a tag in this app,
        encrypted data must have already be written into the tag,
        an empty tag or a tag with only text records written in it.\n
        Any other kind of data written on the tag can not be read by this app,
        as this app is not designed to read all types.\n
        Make sure to have NFC turned on in the device\'s settings before continuing with the help guide.\n
        To read the contents of a tag, simply scan the tag by placing it near the device.
        (for more information on where is the NFC reader on this device, please refer to the device\'s manual or google it).\n
        A password prompt will come up if encrypted data was written previously into tag otherwise
        it will simply show the records in the order they we were written into it.
        </string>
    <string name="write_help_title">How to write and encrypt data into a tag</string>
    <string name="write_help_desc">To write and encrypt data into an NFC tag, 2 perquisites are required:\n
        1: A device that supports NFC tag reading and writing.(This should already be achieved as the app can not be installed otherwise).\n
        2: An NFC tag that supports NDEF technology(check the seller of the tag for more information).\n
        On the WRITE tab records (texts) can be added and both a password and a confirmation are required to encrypt that data into the tag.
    </string>
    <string name="copy_help_title">How to copy tags</string>
    <string name="copy_help_desc">Copying data between tags should work with all sorts of data as long as the payload is not empty.\n
        Copying encrypted tags does not require reentering the password as it is copying the encrypted binary as it is.\n
        To copy a tag: first press the copy button and a copy prompt will show up.\n
        place the tag with data near the device then wait for the next prompt to place the other tag to paste the contents into it.
    </string>
    <string name="remove_help_title">How to remove password from tags</string>
    <string name="remove_help_desc">To remove passwords from a tag, first press the remove password button and wait for the prompt
        then place the encrypted tag to read it\'s contents and decrypt the data.\n
        After decrypting the tag a new prompt to paste the new data will show up.\n
        Place the tag again (or another tag if wanted) to write the data as text records. (these text records can be read by any device)</string>
    <string name="erase_help_title">How to erase the content of a tag</string>
    <string name="erase_help_desc">To erase the contents of a tag simply press the erase button and wait for the prompt.\n
        Then place the tag near the device and the contents will be deleted.\n
        Notice that this action cannot be undone and the records on the tag are permanently deleted.</string>

</resources>
